[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "How significant could that be, of Trayvon Martin's DNA I should say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "And what would be the purpose of Saran wrap and Vaseline?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I was going to try to seal the chest wound, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Tom Mesereau, from all that you've seen so far, would you rather be in the defense or the prosecution camp?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Well, Piers, because the law so much favors the defense, I mean, this is one of the best self-defense statutes for a defendant I've ever seen and it's one of the most pro-defense states in America when it comes to raising self- defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Mesereau"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "RB", "RBR", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "But this is where, Thomas, that Florida is probably the best possible place in America that George Zimmerman could wish to be tried because, as you say, the statute of law there is so heavily skewed in his favor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, yes, and also remember, the burden of proof which applies in every state of America is beyond any reasonable doubt.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Thomas", "George Zimmerman"], "LOCATION": ["Florida", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "How much could that in the end sway, do you think, this final decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, I think their heart must go out to the parents, especially the mother of the deceased Trayvon Martin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Do you think it's right that she'd been thrown to the wolves in the way that she has?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Well, I think you're absolutely right, Piers, me included.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "I've asked this to a few guests before, but do you believe in the context of all this going on this week, is America in your view a more or less racist country since Barack Obama first got elected president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, as I said, I think we've mentioned -- we made tremendous progress, but I think we also see how the president has been treated when people stand up in Congress and say you lie.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Joel, how are you how?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Hey, doing great, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "What were you thinking standing there watching this guy risking his life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "You know, I was like millions of other Americans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "If he had fallen, what would you have said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "You know, I didn't really think about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "What did you say to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, Piers, I prayed that God would give him strength and skill and that the gifts God had given him would come out to the full, that he would have focus and not be distracted -- just he would be at his best and the top of his game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Pretty awesome, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "It really is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB"], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Are you going to be buying a pair of his jeans, which have now become the hottest jeans apparently in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I didn't know that, but maybe I will!", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Will you be with him every step of the way on these?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Oh, I would love to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "What is going on in his head right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What's going on in this guy's head?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I -- the one thing I can tell you is it's not an addiction to something like a high -- high risk that sort of thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 300, "question": "So it's fame?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "And many --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "And we can have one of the most powerful political positions in America, held by somebody who will be sending -- let's be honest -- photos of his wiener to other strange women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ":", "NN", "POS", "VB", "JJS", ":", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "They learn to perhaps be more circumspect and careful but they don't change substantively.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Does that work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Does not work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "From America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I'm not getting 460 calories.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "It's all very well, you're saying no to the yummy but I mean, you take the yummy out of life, what are you left with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Listen, your point is well taken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "JJS", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Well, because I found out the facts and the facts are my initial thinking was like most Americans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Sanjay Gupta, who's seen as a very respected medical guy, he's very firmly, look, there is no evidence that he's seen that marijuana is any more harmful than alcohol or tobacco, and on that basis, why should it be treated differently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "But that's a bizarre argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay Gupta"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Are those -- are those limbs, are those organizations going to pick up cannabis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Well, that's the issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "What am I left with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I didn't say that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Did it work and are you in favor of legalizing cannabis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Piers, obviously it did not work and it's not working now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Patrick Kennedy"]}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "You know, I'd be curious to find out how -- Mr. Kennedy, how prison helped you beat addiction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WRB", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Well, let's ask Patrick Kennedy to answer that very question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130625pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "CD", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Which is -- which is less harmful to America's national interest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "The good news is those aren't our two only options.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]